

Arifur Rahman Arif

Full Stack Web Developer

Confident and positive minded individual with great communication and interpersonal skills who recently graduated an one year full-time training in Full stack Web Development with programming skills in JavaScript, HTML5, CSS3 and NodeJS. Curious about new technologies and looking for a new challenge within the digital industry.

ararif.aa@gmail.com

Berlin, Germany

in linkedin.com/in/arifur-rahman-arif-416735131

+4917621649289

arifur-ra.github.io/MyPortfolio/

github.com/arifur-ra

EDUCATION BACKGROUND

Full Stack Wed Developer DCI-Digital Career Institute gGmbH

07/2020 - 07/2021

Berlin, Germany

Courses

- Accomplishing a one-year-full-time training including technologies from MERN stack
- Completing multiple small and one final large practical project to practice programming skills
- Taking German lesson as part of course in level B2

Bsc in Computer Sceince

Stamford University Bangladesh

09/2007 - 05/2012

Dhaka, Bangladesh

Courses

- o Completed 4 years Bachelor degree with Final Thesis
- Evaluation of the Quality of Voice Over Internet Protocol (VOIP)
 Service with respect to Varying Encoding Techniques
- Graduating with a GPA of 3.57

WORK EXPERIENCE

Sales Man

Galeries Lafayette

06/2018 - 04/2020

Tasks

 Showcased product features to customers and discussed technical details to overcome objections and lock in sales.

Service Staff (Waiter)

Gasthaus Gottlob

01/2015 - 05/2018

Tasks

 Providing excellent wait service to ensure satisfaction. Taking coustomer orders and delivering food and beverages. Making menu recommendations, answering questions and sharing additional information with restaurant patrons.

SKILLS



RELEVANT PROJECT

Sell Your Records (02/2021 - Present)

- E-commerce Web Application
- Its all about music, people can buy and sell all kind of music using this platform.
- Technologies used: React, Java Script, NodeJS, ExpressJs, Materials-UI, MongoDB

Simple To-Do-App (12/2020 - 01/2021)

- Simple Adding and Deleting the List
- Technologies used: React, JavaScript, CSS, HTML

LANGUAGES

English

Professional Working Proficiency

German

Limited Working Proficiency

Bangla

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

HOBBIES

I would like to Play Badminton, Cricket & Billiards.

I would like to travel around the world.